Register of the Wisconsin. State Board of Assessors: Appeal Files, 1992, 1994
Wisconsin Historical Society
Wisconsin. State Board of Assessors: Appeal Files, 19921994
Wisconsin. State Board of Assessors.
Series 2750; 2004/076
2.0 c.f. (2 record center cartons); plus additions of 1.4 c.f.
Wisconsin Historical Society Archives
Records of appeals made to the State Board of Assessors under Wis. Stats. 70.995(8)(c) or (d), generally consisting of the original objection form filed by appellants, associated correspondence, and documentation of the Boards actions. The appeals were filed by individuals or corporations objecting to the amount, valuation, or taxability of manufacturing property, or to penalties issued for late or nonfiling of property report forms.
This collection was received in multiple parts and is organized into 2 major parts. These materials have not been physically interfiled and researchers might need to consult more than one part to locate similar materials.
Part 1 (Series 2750): Original Collection, 1992
Part 2 (2004/076): Additions, 1994
Administrative/Restriction Information
2001/098, 2004/076
Contents List
- Part 1 (Series 2750): Original Collection, 1992, Series 2750; 2.0 c.f. (2 record center cartons)
  Numerical by appeal number.
  - 001-75-C-92 - Technology Plastics (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 002-75-E-92 - Liquid Air Corporation (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 003-75-E-92 - Liquid Air (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 004-75-R-92 - Jackson-Oshkosh Leasing (Medalist) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 005-75-E-92 - 012-75-E-92 - Liquid Air Corp. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 013-75-E-92 - 015-75-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 016-75-E-92 - 017-75-E-92 - Liquid Air Corp. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 018-75-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 019-75-P-92 - Quad/Graphics, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 020-75-P-92 - Integrated Imaging, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 021-75-R-92 - 022-75-R-92 - Manitowoc Co., Inc (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 023-75-R-92 - Midwest Properties (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 024-75-P-92 - Kickhaefer Manufacturing Co. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 025-75-C-92 - Dodge Construction Co., Inc. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 101-76-R-92 - Lippert Components, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 102-76-P-92 (withdrawn) - Wisconsin Foam Products, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 103-76-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 104-76-R-92 - United States Shoe Corp. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 105-76-E-92 - Liquid Air Corp. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 106-76-R-92 - Madison-Kipp Corp. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 107-76-P-92 - Colman Motor Products, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 108-76-P-92 - OMC Parts and Accessories (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 109-76-P-92 - OHMEDA (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 110-76-P-92 - Celtics, LTD (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 111-76-R-92 - Gardner Baking Co. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 112-76-R-92 - Nicolet Instrument Corp. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 113-76-R-92 - Carl A. Mancini, Agent - Trustee of Living Trust (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 114-76-R-92 - William L. Zinga (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 201-77-C-92 - Midwest Bleachers (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 202-77-E-92 - Liquid Air (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 203-77-C-92 - American Plasma Centers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 204-77-R-92 - Equitable Real Estate (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 205-77-C-92 - Milwaukee Blood Plasma (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 206-77-R-92 - 208-77-R-92 - Lignego Brothers West Allis (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 209-77-P-92 - Bailey Metals Corp. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 210-77-E-92 - 211-77-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 212-77-R-92 - Schendel Corp. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 213-77-E-92 - 214-77-E-92 - Liquid Air Corp. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 215-77-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 216-77-P-92 - Global Manufacturing Corp. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 217-77-R-92 - Midwest Fire Protection, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 218-77-P-92 - Journal/Sentinel, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 219-77-R-92 - PPG Industries, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 220-77-R-92 - G.E. Medical Systems Group (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 221-77-P-92 - 222-77-P-92 - Square D Company (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 223-77-R-92 - Prime Leather Finishes Co. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 224-77-R-92 - Fallon/Pressing (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 225-77-P-92 - IGL-Wisconsin Awning, Tent and Trailer Co. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 226-77-R-92 - Charles E. and Lorena J. Cottrill (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 227-77-R-92 - Christos Kambouris (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 228-77-P-92 - Nowakowski, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 229-77-P-92 - Foto Fast One Hour Photo Processing, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 230-77-R-92 - William and Lois Gould (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 231-77-R-92 - William Peters (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 501-78-C-92 - Van Slett Craftsmen (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 502-78-C-92 - Star Automation (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 503-78-R-92 - Westoc Assoc. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 504-78-E-92 - Cardox Corporation (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 506-78-E-92 - Liquid Air (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 505-78-R-92 - Chrysler Corporation (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 507-78-R-92 - Alloy Casting Co. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 508-78-R-92 - 511-78-R-92 - Milwaukee Solvents and Chemicals Corp. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 512-78-R-92 - C.S.M. Brookfield Inv. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 513-78-P-92 (withdrawn) - Treeline CNC, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 514-78-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 515-78-P-92 - Polydyne, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 516-78-E-92 - AGA Gas, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 517-78-P-92 - 519-78-P-92 - Quad/Graphics (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 520-78-R-92 - Styberg Engineering Co. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 521-78-R-92 (withdrawn) - BCF Investment Co. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 522-78-R-92 (withdrawn) - Wacker Corp. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 523-78-R-92 - Burke Products, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 701-79-C-92 - Dome Petroleum (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 702-79-R-92 - Link Recreational, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 703-79-UR-92 - Village of Norwalk (Swiss Valley Farms) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 704-79-R-92 - Jennico, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 705-79-R-92 - Prairie Sand and Gravel, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 706-79-R-92 - BTI, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 707-79-E-92 - Liquid Air (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 708-79-E-92 - Liquid Air (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 709-79-R-92 - Phillips Plastics (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 710-79-UR-92 - Town of St. Joseph (Brown County) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 711-79-R-92 - Haas Sons, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 712-79-UR-92 - Town of Minong (Washington County) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 713-79-R-92 - Uniroyal Goodrich Tire Co. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 714-79-R-92 - Presto Industries, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 715-79-R-92 - National Presto Industries, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 716-79-R-92 (Withdrawn) - Phillips Plastic Corp. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 717-79-P-92 - Safeway Stores, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 801-81-C-92 - Integrated Imaging (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 802-81-R-92 - Lakes Precision, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 803-81-P-92 - Point Publishing, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 804-81-E-92 - 810-81-E-92 - Liquid Air Corp. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 811-81-E-92 - 812-81-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 813-81-E-92 - Cardox Corp. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 814-81-R-92 - New Linwood, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 815-81-P-92 - TGW Inc. of Wisconsin (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 816-81-R-92 (withdrawn) - Gerald and Sally Germain c/o TGW Inc. of Wisconsin (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 817-81-P-92 - Con Agra Fresh Meats, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 818-81-R-92 - Con Agra Fresh Meats, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 819-81-P-92 - Green Bay Cheese Co. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 820-81-P-92 - Outboard Marine Corp. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 821-81-R-92 - Fiskars Manufacturing Corp. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 822-81-R-92 - 825-81-R-92 - Re Pap Wisconsin, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 826-81-R-92 - Riverside Paper Company (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 827-81-P-92 - Metro Graphic Press, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 828-81-R-92 - VICOM, LTD (Midwest Wire) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 829-81-R-92 - Wausau Daily Herald (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 830-81-R-92 - Gannett Satellite Information Network (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 831-81-P-92 - Central Tool and Manufacturing Inc. (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Part 2 (2004/076): Additions, 1994, 2004/076; 1.4 c.f. (1 record center carton and 1 archives box); 1993 files were never received from the Record Center.
  1994 appeal files arranged alphabetically by company name.
  Among the companies represented are Del Monte, Pitney Bowes, and Quad Graphics. Box 1 contains A-Q; Box 2 contains R-Z.
  - 804-81-R-94 - Frank Faehna, American Wood Fibers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 815-81-R-94 - Appleton Papers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1006-76-94 - BM Investments (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 203-77-P-94 - Bailey Metals Corp. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 202-77-P-94 - Barefoot International, Ltd. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 505-78-P-94 - Butler Gear Co. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 711-79-R-94 - Benchmark Components, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 217-77-R-94 - Church Metal Spinning Co., Inc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1004-78-94 - Clarence Hense, c/o Midland Plastics (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1011-75-94 - Commerce Drive Co. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 803-81-R-94 - Con Agra Fresh Meats (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 807-81-R-94 - Consolidated Papers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 102-76-C-94 - City of Edgerton (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 208-77-R-94 - Damson/Birtcher Realty Income (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Del Monte Corp.
    - 001-75-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 002-75-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 808-81-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1003-81-94 - M. De Matteo Construction Co. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 701-79-P-94 - Dyno Overlays, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 215-77-R-94 - EI Building Account (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 104-76-R-94 - Elko Solutions, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 211-77-R-94 - Emmber Foods, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 209-77-R-94 - Enco Realty Co., Inc. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 006-75-R-94 - F.B. Leasing Co. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 712-79-R-94 - Food Service Products Co. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 110-76-R-94 - Frito-Lay, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 109-76-R-94 - GENTRAC, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 702-79-R-94 - Susan Girdhari (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1005-78-94 - Louise C. Grier (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1001-77-94 - Thomas Harrington (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 005-75-R-94 - Heresite Protective Coatings (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 502-78-C-94 - S.C. Johnson (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 503-78-P-94 - Milton King, Centurion Ind. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 506-78-R-94 - MTI International (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Spiro Mehail
    - 504-78-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 1002-78-94 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Micronetics International, Inc.
    - 1007-77-94 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 205-77-P-94 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 008-75-R-94 - Midwest Properties (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Associated Milk Producers, Inc.
    - 707-79-P-94 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 111-76-P-94 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Moore's Food Products (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 710-79-R-94 - National Presto Industries, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 216-77-P-94 - Nightrider Overnite Copy Service (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 007-75-P-94 - Oshkosh Truck Corp. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 501-78-C-94 - Payne and Dolan (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 219-77-P-94 - Peter Plybeah, Midwest Printing (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 805-81-R-94 - Patz Industrial Corp. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 201-77-C-94 - Paving Mix and Construction (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 508-78-P-94 - Pitney Bowes Credit Corp. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1010-81-94 - Plover Investment Group (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1012-77-94 - Peter Plybeah (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 802-81-P-94 - Point Publications (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 210-77-R-94 - Prime Leather Finishes Co. (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Quad/Graphics, Inc.
    - 519-78-P-94 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - 214-77-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 009-75-R-94 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 801-81-P-94 - Quick Signs, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 518-78-P-94 - Quirk Realty Holdings (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 003-75-R-94 - Royal Terrace Partnership, c/o Paragon Electric (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 206-77-P-94 - Schlitz Furnaces, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 207-77-P-94 - Schlitz Studios, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 517-78-R-94 - Silgan Containers Corp. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 522-78-P-94 - Snap-On Tools Corp. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1013-75-94 - TAB Services Corp. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 812-81-R-94 - Tape, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 705-79-R-94 - United for Excellence (UFE), Inc. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 103-76-P-94 - Uniroyal Technology Corp. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vanier Graphics Corp.
    - 1008-78-94 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 516-78-P-94 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 218-77-R-94 - Estate of Gene Verhein (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 101-76-C-94 - W.K. Construction (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 814-81-P-94 - WSA, Inc. - Linetec Division (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 525-78-P-94 - Zermac, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 220-77-R-94 - Joseph and Vera Zilber (Box 2, Folder 16)